Guide to the James E. Dyer Papers MS 052
Western Connecticut State University Archives and Special Collections
- Series I: Personal and Family Papers, RG6.xx___x
  - Subseries B: Thomas Dyer (Father) Materials, RG6.xx___x
    - In Gratitude to Mr. Democrat 1977, Thomas J. Dyer, For Outstanding Contributions to the Democratic Party, Jefferson-Jackson Day Dinner (plaque) (Box 25)
    - The Old timers' Athletic Association of Greater Danbury Civic Award Presented to Thomas Dyer For His Many Contributions To The Community (plaque), 1977 (Box 25)
    - State of Connecticut General Assembly, House Joint Resolution No. 171 (framed), 1977 (Box OS 2)
    - Danbury Council of Veterans Resolution, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence, 90th Birthday, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - In grateful appreciation for over 30 years of dedicated service to the Danbury Veterans Council (Plaque), 1985-1995 (Box 25)
    - Memorial Day Service and Parade, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Thank You Letters from children, Garden Street School, Brewster, NY, 1993-1994 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence (includes copy of Danbury and Our boys in the World War by Anna Hornik), 1994 (Box 9, Folder 1-2)
    - Memorial Day Parade, "Thomas Dyer, Veteran, World War I" ID and Ribbon, 1994 (Box 22)
    - Correspondence, Notes and Eulogy, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 3-6)
  - Subseries C: Mary Dyer (Mother) Materials, RG6.xx___x
    - Certified Copy of Birth Record, May 14, 1900 [1964] (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Certificate To Enter Newtown High School, 1911 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Newtown High School, Class of 1917 (Handwritten Speech) (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Marriage License (copy), 1927 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Certificate of Marriage, 1927 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Wedding Gift Card "Sincerest Wishes for a long and happy wedded life. From your old pals of P. & A.", 1927 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Prayer Card, "Infant Dyer, Died February 4, 1929" (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Proclamation 50th Anniversary, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Map of Property prepared for Mary Dyer, Town of Newtown, Fairfield County, Conn., 1984 (Item 35)
    - Map: Town of Newtorn Map Showing Land Released to Mary J. Dyer et al by The State of Connecticut, 1985 (Box OS 13)
    - Clippings, 60th Anniversary, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - JD Notes, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Ellis Island Certificate of Registration In The American Immigrant Wall of Honor, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Funeral Registry, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 18-19)
    - Tribute by JD, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Condolence Cards, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 2-4)
    - Perpetual Remembrances, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 5-8)
  - Subseries D: Dyer Family Photographs, RG6.xx___x
    - Miscellaneous Danbury Images, ca.1900 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - "Newtown, Connecticut, One Room School House" (Mary J. Murphy standing first row far right), ca.1910 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - TJD leaning against railing, large floral decorated clock in background (unlabeled), ca.1925 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - TJD/MM Wedding Portrait (one 7.5 x 9.5 b/w mounted) Frame located in Box 25., 1927 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - TJD/MM Bridal Party (one 4x5 b/w negative), 1927 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Collage of photographs and clipppings of Thomas and Mary Dyer (24.5x30.5 framed), ca.1930 (Item 34)
    - JD Studio portrait (about 9 months) 12 x 14 tinted w/mat, 1947 (Box OS 11)
    - JD with TJD (5x7 b/w, framed), 1951 (Box 38)
    - JD and TJD in Washington, DC (three 3.5x5 and one 2.5x3.5 b/w), ca.1955 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Grammar School, Hayestown Avenue School, Class of 1958 photograph (6x8 color, labeled) (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - JD in front of Kennedy-Johnson poster and U. S.Capitol (two 3x4 b/w polaroid), 1960 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Izzy Singer w/handwritten message (one 8x10 b/w), undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - TJD Delegates to WW I Convention, Buffalo, NY, 9/23-26,1962 (3.5x3.5 b/w labeled) (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Scott Fanton Junior Curator's field trip to Bridgeport Museum (one 4x5 b/w negative), 1963 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Danbury High School (one 3.5x3.5 b/w labeled), 1963-1964 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - JD w/Julian Bond 7/69; JED reading Profiles in Courage 1969; Valentine Dance with Jeanne Bechard 1966; DHS campaign 1964; Morris Street Elementary School lecture on JFK 1966; Norwalk Community College Portrait (9 various sizes 2.5x3.5 to 5x7 b/w and color), 1964-1969 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - TJD Forty-Three Years Later, 24th Engineers A.E.F. (one 8x10 b/w), ca.1965 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - "Smiles" Dyer (TJD's brother w/unknown person) 8x10 b/w, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - TJD Swearing In (one 5x7 b/w), 1975 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - JD with TJD and note from Jayne Holmes (one 3.5x4.5 color), 1981 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - JD and AD (one 5x7 b/w), 1983 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - JD with Owen ? (one 3.5x3.5 clor), 1983 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - JD with TJD and MMD (four 5x7 b/w and one 5x7 color), 1983-1986 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - JD/AW Wedding Portrait (11x14 b/w matted), 1985 (Box 38)
    - JD/AW "Thank You for your lovely gift" (one 3.5x7 color), 1985 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - TJD outdoors in a crowd, possibly Memorial or Veteran's Day (two 8x10 b/w), ca.1985 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - TJD and JD, one 3.5x5 color (framed), ca.1990 (Box 25)
    - "Thank You!" card (JD and AD holding Christopher, 4x6 color on 7x10 card, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Thomas Dyer with various individuals (one 5x7, three 4x6 and four 3.5x5 color), 1993-1994 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Dyer Children 24 various sizes (2.5x3.5 to 4x6 color), 1993-2008 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - JD with book "when the LEAVES begin to TURN" (one 8x12 b/w), 1996 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - JD and Rose ? at Tom Green Dinner (one 4x6 color), 2003 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - JD's children, posed (framed), ca.2003 (Box 38)
    - Dyer Family, Various Events, 1955-1983 (Box 39.1, Folder 1)
      General note
      17 various sizes (3.5x2.5 to 8x10 b/w and color phtographs
    - Dyer Family, Various Events, 1975-1990 (Box 39.1, Folder 2)
      17 various sizes (3.5x5 to 5x7 b/w and color photographs
    - "Dad's 90th Birthday", 1985 (Box 39.1, Folder 3)
      19 5x7 b/w, 8 b/w contact sheets
  - Subseries E: Dyer Familey Audio and Video, RG6.xx___x
    - Dyer Research Development (three reel/reel recordings), 1959-1962 (Box 12)
      Reel to reel tape recording
    - Evelyn Lincoln discusses her new book on CBS (cassette tape), 1965 (Box 12)
      Cassette Tape
    - JD at WiNE Radio Station, event unknown (reel/reel recording), 1967 (Box 12)
    - JD Speech at Morris Street School, Danbury, CT, to Commemorate JFK's 50th Birthday (reel/reel recording), 1967 (Box 12)
    - TJD, guest on The Inside Story over WLAD (reel/reel recording), 1977 (Box 12)
    - Mayor and Mrs. James Dyer Wedding, September 15, 1985 (VHS) (Box 12)
      VHS
    - WW I Music, TJD plays piano at Danbury High School (VHS), 1994 (Box 12)
  - Subseries F: Kennedy Memorabilia, RG6.xx___x
    - "Leadership for the "60's, Kennedy Johnson" Pennant, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - JFK Radio-TV Address, August 13, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - "The President's House" JFK White House matches, 1962 (Box 22)
    - The John F. Kennedy Center For The Performing Arts (press information), 1962 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Morey, Emil J. Letter, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - JFK Library: Presidential Recordings Cassette Tapes: A-1 to A-4 Integration of the University of Mississippi; B-1 to B-7 Tax Cut Proposals; C-1 Kennedy & Shriver on Peace Corps 4/2/1963; D-1 Cuban Missille Crisis Meeting 10/16/1962; E 1-9 Civil Rights (two copies). Collection given to JD by Emil J. Morey 1983. 31 cassette tapes, 1962-1963 (Box 24)
    - JFK Library: Papers of John F. Kennedy, Presidential Papers, President's Office Files, Presidential Recordings, Index to Cassette Tapes A 1-4 Integration of the University of Mississippi and B 1-7 Tax Cut Proposal, 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - JFK Library: Papers of John F. Kennedy, Presidential Papers, President's Office Files, Presidential Recordings, Transcripts, Integration of University of Mississippi, 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - JFK Library: Papers of John F. Kennedy, Presidential Papers, President's Office Files, Presidential Recordings, Transcripts, Tax Cut Proposals, Volume I, 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - JFK Library: Papers of John F. Kennedy, Presidential Papers, President's Office Files, Presidential Recordings, Transcripts, Tax Cut Proposals, Volume II, 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - JFK Library: Papers of John F. Kennedy, Presidential Papers, President's Office Files, Presidential Recordings, Transcripts, Tax Cut Proposals, Volume III, 1962-1963 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - JFK Library: Papers of John F. Kennedy, Presidential Papers, President's Office Files, Presidential Recordings, Transcripts, Kennedy-Shriver Conversation on the Peace Corps, April 2, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - JFK Library: Papers of John F. Kennedy, Presidential Papers, President's Office Files, Presidential Recordings, Transcripts, Cuban Missile Crisis Meetings, October 16, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - JFK Library: Papers of John F. Kennedy, Presidential Papers, President's Office Files, Presidential Recordings, Logs and Transcripts, Civil Rights, 1963 (two copies) (Box 13, Folder 11-12)
    - JFK Gravesite (design, fact sheets, and five 8x10 b/w photographs), 1964 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Clippings, 1964-1971 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - JFK Exhibits, 1965-1970 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Evelyn Lincoln, President Kennedy's Secretary; Correspondence, Clippings,Greeting Cards, Photographs, 1966-2005 (Box 14, Folder 4-6)
    - Speech, Kiwanis Club Luncheon to Commemorate JFK's 49th Birthday, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Speech/Exhibit, Morris Street School, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Bobby for President Mug, 1967 (Box 25)
    - Kennedy Hobby Club, 1968-1970 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - RFK Prayer Card, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - RFK Memorabilia: Kennedy Bumper Sticker and "Kennedy, Make your vote count on May 7th" Citizens for Kennedy, New Albany, IN (3 copies), 1968 (Box OS 11)
    - Clippings and JFK Memorial Speech, 1969-1975 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Edward M. Kennedy Campaign Pins, 1968-1972 (Box 93)
    - Edward M. Kennedy '72 Committee, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Edward M.Kennedy Miscellany, 1973-2005 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - JFK Collectors, 1973-1975 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - JFK Library Paperweight, ca.1979 (Box 25)
    - Jackie and Municipal Art Society, 1993-2001 (Box 15, Folder 1-4)
    - Jackie Kennedy, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 5-6)
    - JFK Auction, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 7-8)
    - JFK, Jr. Clippings, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - JFK 1960 Election Stats, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Re-Dedication of Kennedy Park, Danbury,CT, May 29, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - John F. Kennedy Exhibit, Certificate of Authenticity, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Series II: WestConn Materials, RG6.xx___x
  - Normal School and Midtown Campus (aerial view) Two 3.5x5.5 post cards, ca.1915-1940 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Research Papers, 1967-1971 (Box 16, Folder 2-3)
  - ID cards (Library, WXCI, Chi Epsilon, Alumni, Board of Trustees, etc.), 1968-1991 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, Committee to End the War, 1969-1970 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Echo (issues removed and placed in Student Publications) see below for dates, 1969-1982 (Item 3)
  - Posters for SGA President (four 9.5 x 14), 1969-1971 (Box 37)
  - Campaign Pins (9 pins) and "Wesconn Indians" (1 pin), 1969-1976 (Box 24)
  - Clippings, 1969-1976 (Box 16, Folder 6-7)
  - Let's Vote 18 (clippings), 1969-1970 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - SGA Campaign, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - SGA Election, Karen Burns/Dave Jewett Campaign, speeches, and Dyer Daily April 8 and 9, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 8-10)
  - SGA Election, Karen Burns/Dave Jewett Campaign, speeches, and Dyer Daily April 8 and 9, 1969 (Box OS 11)
  - "WCS" Blue and White Beanie, 1969 (Box 22)
  - Delta Tau Kappa, Epsilon Rho Chapter, May 28, 1970 (certificate) (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - "Keep Tuition Down" Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Name plate from BOT main office, 80 Pratt Street, Hartford, 1970-1973 (Box 92)
  - The National Student Register Certificate, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - The News-Times "Wesconn student given state post" (front page dated January 28, 1970, 18x25 mounted on wood/acrylic coated) (Item 6)
  - Open House Program October 18, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Proclamations upon becoming member of the Board of Trustees signed by Gov. John Dempsey and Ella Grasso (2), 1970-1975 (Box OS 3)
  - Speeches, Notes, Drafts, Clippings, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 14-17)
  - State of Connecticut, Official Business, Board of Trustees (parking sign), 1970-1973 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Trustee clippings, 1970-1975 (Box 16, Folder 19-20)
  - White House Conference on Children, Report to the President and Program (book), 1970 (Box 89)
  - White House Conference on Children (16x24 poster), 1970 (Box OS 12)
  - White House Conference on Children Program, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 1-2)
  - White House Conference on Children Follow-Up, 1970-1971 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Who's Who Among Students in American Universities and Colleges Employment Questionnaire and Orientation Program, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Who's Who Among Students in American Universities and Colleges (plaque), 1970-1973 (Box 26)
  - Correspondence (ALS Ruth A. Haas), 1971-1975 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Alumni Award for Outstanding Service to Western Connecticut State College (Pewter Mug), 1971 (Box 95)
  - Governor's Prayer Breakfast, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Honors Assembly Program, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Robert F. Kennedy Journalism Award (pamphlet), 1971 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Robert's rules of order revised (book), 1971 (Box 90)
  - SCSC Commencement Program, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Speeches: Keep Tuition Down, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 4-5)
  - Trustees' Stationery, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Tuition Clippings, 1971-1972 (Box 17, Folder 11-12)
  - "a YEARBOOK Remembers" Poster, 1971 (Box OS 11)
  - Press Releases, Notes and Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 17, Folder 13-18)
  - Speeches, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 1-2)
  - Speeches, 1972-1973 (Box 18, Folder 3-5)
  - Speeches (notes), 1972-1973 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Staff Organization for Yearbook Editor, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Board of Trustees "Battle" Clippings, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - The Choice Newsletter, 1973 (Box OS 5)
  - Correspondence, Newsletters (ALS Ruth A. Haas, William R. Ratchford), 1973-1975 (Box 18, Folder 7-9)
  - The Hartford Courant, "Austerity Blights College Campuses" (front page dated July 22, 1973, 18x25 mounted on wood/acrylic coated) (Item 7)
  - A Report On the Open Forum Meetings and State College Tours of State College Trustee James Dyer, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - '73 Scrap, Our First Year and Why Build It Now, 1973-1975 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Speeches, Notes, Correspondence, Commencement Programs, etc., 1973 (Box 18, Folder 12-15)
  - Speech/Notes, ECSC Leadership Banquet, May 2, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Yearbook Suggestions, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Columbia Scholastic Press Association, Yearbook '74 Second Place Certificate (6/x8 mounted), 1974 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Campus Search Committee CLOSED (One 5x7 b/w photograph of Dr. Bersi placed in the WCSC Photograph File. One copy of the Daily Planet, California State College Dominguez Hills newspaper placed in OS Box 10), 1974-1975 (Box 19, Folder 1-6)
  - Clippings, 1974-1975 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence (ALS George McGovern, Hubert Humphrey, Ted Kennedy, Sargent Shriver, Abe Ribicoff, Ella Grasso, Robert Bersi), 1974-1975 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Quality of Life for Connecticut Children Conference, April 27, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - SCSC Rape Stories, 1974-1975 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - SGA Certificate of Appreciation, 1974-1975 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence (Ruth A. Haas, includes invitation to Ruth A. Haas Testimonial Dinner), 1975 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Trustees, Westconn Campus Campaign, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Trustees releases, clippings, and correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Wesconn Alumni Association Annual Meeting Programs, 1975-1976 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Remarks of State College Trustee James Dyer Before the Education Committee, March 5, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1977-1979 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - A History of Western Connecticut State College, Danbury, Connecticut 1903-1978 by Charlotte H. Isham (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - In Appreciation and Gratitude for your Support, Chi Epsilon Sigma (plaque), 1978 (Box 26)
  - Alumnus of the Year Award (plaque), 1980 (Box 26)
  - Correspondence re Stephen Feldman CLOSED, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Memorial Service for Ruth A. Haas, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1987-1991 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Centennial Correspondence, 2001-2002 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Dr. Eric Roman, Retirement Dinner Program and Obituary, 2006-2007 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Robert P. DiNardo Memorial Fund, 2009 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - SCSC Leadership Banquet Speech 5/2/1973, Cassette Tape (Box 23)
  - SCSC Forum (cassette tape), 1973 (Box 23)
  - Side 1: 11/15/1973, WiLI Radio Talk Show, Willimantic; Side 2: 12/21/1973, St. Peter's 8th Grade Class lecture on politics (cassette tape) (Box 23)
  - VFW Speech 11/10/1973 (cassette tape), 1975 (Box 23)
  - Side 1: Assoc. of Conn. Address at SCSC, New Haven 10/26/1973; Side 2: WCSC Outdoor Rally Faculty Firings 5/10/1973 Speech (cassette tape) (Box 23)
  - Side 1: WCSU Commencement 5/27/1973, Side 2: Last BOT meeting 6/4/1973, and press coverage of 6/2/1973 and 7/19/1973 (cassette tape) (Box 23)
  - Side 1: JD and ? 1/31/74-2/1/74 SCSC Rapes Reaction and 2/10/74 WDKC. Side 2: 1974 WCSC to NY Class of 1976 (cassette tape), 1974-1976 (Box 23)
  - Yale-CTV and Cable TV, 1/26/1975 Interview (cassette tape) (Box 23)
  - Student Life: Our Latin American Neighbors, Dr. Jenkins w/students on field trip, "New Project" and women's gym class (four b/w various sizes, 8x10 to 3.5x5 b/w), ca.1920-1944 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - SGA Election, labeled/unlabelled (two 5x5 b/w and 11 3.5x5 color), 1970 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    Photographs
  - Board of Trustees Appointment: JD, TD, and Gov. Dempsey (one 8x10 and one 5x5 b/w), 1970 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - JD in Yearbook Office (8x10 b/w), 1970 (Box 37)
  - WCSC Strike Vote (two 5x7 b/w), 1970 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - White House Conference on Children, JD as BOT Member, Channel 8 and Channel 3 (one 5x7 and one 4x4 b/w), 1970 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - JD in cap and gown (one 8x10 b/w), 1971 (Box 37)
  - Anti-Tuition Rally (one 8x10 and four 5x7 b/w), 1971 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Education Committee Hearing on Tuition Dec. 10, 1971 (one 4.5x6.5 b/w) (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - JD Announcing Results of Football Referendum (one 4x4 b/w), 1971 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - JD in Yearbook Office (one 8x10 b/w), 1971 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Yearbook 1971 (six 5x7 b/w) (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - JD "At Eastern" (one 8x10 b/w), 1973 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - SCSC Commencement (one 8x10 b/w), 1973 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - SCSC Forum as State College Trustee (one 6.5x7.5 b/w), 1973 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - CCSC, State College Forum (one 8x10 b/w), 1973 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Yearbook Office, JD and Mary Beth Marckowski (one 5x7 b/w), 1973 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Yearbook 1973 (six 5x7 b/w) (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Year book (seven various sizes mounted on board), 1974-1975 (Box 37)
  - Yearbook 1974 (four 5x7 b/w) (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Robert Bersi, posed, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Ruth Haas Retirement Dinner, labeled (three 5x7 b/w), 1975 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - JFK Park (one 8x10 b/w), 1975 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Yearbook 1975 (15 5x7 b/w) (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Yearbook Miscellaneous (nine various sizes, 5x7-2.5x3 b/w and color), ca.1975 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Yearbook 1976 (three 5x7 b/w) (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Yearbook 1977, Includes Pres. Bersi (one 5x7 b/w and three 3.5x5 color) (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Yearbook 1978 (nine 5x7 b/w) (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Event unknown (one color slide), 1986 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Student Life Negatives (students, classroom, laboratory schools, buildings, events, yearbook, and catalog photographs, indoor/outdoor), 1939-1944 (Box 27, Folder 27-36)
  - Yearbook 1971 Contact sheets/negatives, JD Editor, 1970-1971 (Box 28, Folder 1-12)
    Negatives
  - Yearbook 1972 Contact sheets/negatives (Box 28, Folder 13-17)
    Contact Sheets/negs
  - Yearbook 1972 Contact sheets/negatives, 1972-1973 (Box 29, Folder 1-10)
  - Yearbook 1973 Contact sheets/negatives, JD Chief Photographer (labeled/unlabeled), 1972-1973 (Box 29, Folder 11-16)
  - Yearbook 1973 Contact sheets/negatives, JD Chief Photographer (labeled/unlabeled), 1972-1973 (Box 30, Folder 1-3)
  - Yearbook 1974 Contact sheets/negatives (Box 30, Folder 4-16)
  - Yearbook 1974 Contact sheets/negatives, 1974-1975 (Box 31, Folder 1-6)
  - Yearbook 1975 Contact sheets/negatives, JD Chief Photographer and Designer, 1974-1975 (Box 31, Folder 7-14)
  - Yearbook 1975 Contact sheets/negatives, JD Chief Photographer and Designer (Box 32, Folder 1-17)
  - Yearbook 1975 Color negatives, JD Chief Photographer and Designer (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Yearbook 1976 Contact sheets/negatives (Box 33, Folder 1-18)
    Color Negatives
  - Yearbook 1976 color negatives (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Yearbook 1976-1978 proofs (color) (Box 36)
  - Yearbook 1977 Contact sheets/negatives (Note: JD covered special events; Dave Douyard, Paul Garavel and others did majority of work), 1977-1978 (Box 34, Folder 1-15)
    Proofs
  - Yearbook 1977 color negatives, 1977-1978 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Yearbook 1978 Contact sheets/negatives (Note: Paul Garavel, Editor; Dave Douyard, Asst. Editor; Photographs: James Dyer, Dave Douyard, Paul Garavel, Tom Williams, Layout: Dyer, Douyard, Garavel) labeled/unlabeled, 1977-1978 (Box 34, Folder 17-20)
  - Yearbook 1979 Contact sheets/negatives (Note: Dave Douyard, editor; Mark Chamberlain, Jean Lubus, and Tom Williams) labeled/unlabeled, 1978-1979 (Box 35, Folder 1-17)
  - Echo: 1969: 4/8, 4/15, 9/30, 10/7, 10/21, 10/28; 1970: 3/18, 3/24, 4/9; 4/28, 5/12, 5/26, 10/13, 12/17 (partial); 1972: 3/21, 4/7, 5/10, 9/13 (partial), 11/21 (partial); 1974: 3/21, 5/29, 5/16; 1974: 10/24; 1975: 10/30 (partial); 1976: 9/9; 1982: 4/13, 1969-1972 (Item 3)
  - Echo 3/21/73 and 3/29/72 interfiled within existing collection in A&SC, 1972-1973
    Separated Materials note
    Interfiled with the Student Newspaper Collection RG 5.15
  - Junior Prom, 1970 (Box 39.1, Folder 4)
    One 3x4 color polaroid photograph
  - WCSC Scrapbook, 1969-1971 (Box OS 12)
    104 b/w photographs, various sizes:
    Campaign for SGA V.P. 10/69
    WCSC '71 class meeting
    Trustee appointment 1/70
    JD announcing football referendum results 3/70
    spring strike 5/70
    SGA Budget meetings 5/70
    yearbook staff pictures, spring '70
    Commencement as Trustee '70-71
    Vote 18, Newtown High School 10/70
    JFK Service 11/22/70
    White House Conference 12/70
    Echo office 2/71
    before Education Committee as Trustee 12/10/71
    Education Committee Hearing on Tuition 2/71
    WCSC Awards Assembly 5/71
    Memorial Day 1971
    JFK service 11/71
    Bushnell Park Tuition Rally 11/71.
  - Post-WCSC - Pre-Mayoral Scrapbook, 1971-1976 (Box OS 12)
    150 b/w photographs, various sizes:
    JD candids/posed (SGA office, Graduation 1/1972
    "Keep Tuition Down
    " WCSC Trustee
    SCSC Commencement 1/1972
    Buley Retirement Spring 1972
    Democratic National Committee 1972
    John S. Monagan Campaign Aide 12/72
    JFK Exhibit and voting machine 11/72
    SGA
    JD behind camera 1973
    SCSC Commencement 1973
    State College Forums 2/73
    Echo picnic 1973
    ECSC Awards Banquet 1973
    WCSC Graduation 5/73
    CCSC graduation 6/73